https://nanolight.com/terms-conditions/

login/registermy account4Account DetailsXOrders5Logout
( )
About UsProductsOur TechnologyPublications
Terms of Use
Last Updated: June 9, 2020
This Website located at www.nanolight.com is owned and operated by NanoLight Technologies, a division of Prolume LTD., a Nevada corporation (“this Website”).
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. THESE TERMS OF USE CONSTITUTE A LEGALLY BINDING AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND PROLUME. BY ACCESSING OR USING ANY PART OF THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE SO BOUND, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS WEBSITE.
If you are under the age of 18, please discuss your use of this Website and our Terms of Use with your parent or guardian.
User Conduct
You expressly agree that you will not use this Website or any other internet services provided by Prolume for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices. You agree to abide by all applicable local, state, national, and international laws and regulations. Any unauthorized commercial use of this Website, Prolume’s servers or internet infrastructure is expressly prohibited. You will not use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of this Website as determined by Prolume in its sole discretion.
Privacy
By using this Website, you consent to the terms of Prolume’s Privacy Policy, which you understand may be modified from time to time. The Privacy Policy, which can be reached by clicking on the Privacy Policy link located at the bottom of the Prolume site, is incorporated into these Terms of Use by reference. You consent to Prolume’s use of cookies and similar devices as further described in the Privacy Policy and for the purposes set forth in the Privacy Policy. You further understand and agree that, to the extent that information is collected about you, it will be stored on servers in the United States.
Accounts
You have option of establishing an account on the Website (an “Account”). In addition, you may be required to have an Account to access or participate in some of the features of this Website. You represent and warrant that all information provided in registering your Account is true and accurate. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Account, and for all activities that occur through the use of your Account. You do not own your Account. Under these Terms of Use, you are granted a limited, personal, non-transferable, non-commercial, revocable license to use your Account to access this Website. You may not sell or transfer all or any part of your Account. You may not use your Account in any way that violates these Terms of Use.
We reserve the right to refuse to register you and provide you with an Account and/or to deny you access to the Website for any reason in our sole and absolute discretion. We may terminate or suspend your Account and/or access to all or part of this Website if we, in our sole and absolute discretion, determine that you have breached these Terms of Use or any other rule applicable to the Website or that your conduct violates applicable law or is otherwise harmful to the Website, other persons or us. Any such termination or suspension or removal shall be without liability to you. In addition, we may terminate or suspend your Account and/or access to all or part of this Website if we determine to cease all or a portion of our operations and/or the provision of any applicable products or services in connection with this Website. We reserve the right to change any or all of the features of and activities available on this Website at any time without notice. All such terminations, suspensions, removals and/or changes shall be without any liability to you.
Online Shopping
All purchases are subject to the terms and conditions of these Terms of Use and any additional requirements shown on the product or checkout page or elsewhere on this Website. Customers must be over age 18 with a valid credit card. Website visitors under age 18 cannot make purchases. When a customer places an order, we collect information associated with the transaction in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
Prices: Prices of products and delivery and other charges displayed on this Website are current at the time of issue, but may change at any time without notice and are subject to availability. Stated prices do not include shipping and handling or taxes. You are solely responsible for any sales, local or similar taxes and duties or other liabilities imposed by any governmental agency, including without limitation, any customs duty, goods and services taxes imposed on any products ordered by you from this Website. All prices are stated in United States dollars.
Charges: If you purchase by credit card, we may authorize the amount of your purchase with your credit card issuer at the time you place your order.
Availability: We cannot guarantee availability of product, even if our Website shows that a particular product is available. We may not have all products or product lines available online and we may discontinue products at any time.
Defective Products: At our option, we will replace or refund your purchase price for any product ordered from this Website which is defective upon delivery. You must contact us to report a defective product.
Orders: We reserve the right to refuse or cancel any order you place with us. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order. These restrictions may include orders placed by or under the same customer account, the same credit card, and/or orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. We reserve the right to limit or prohibit orders that, in our sole judgment, appear to be placed by dealers, resellers, or distributors. If your credit card has already been charged for an order at the time the order is rejected, declined or cancelled, we will issue a credit to the credit card account which was charged.
Shipping/Risk of Loss: We will ship your order to the address you provide in compliance with these Terms of Use. You are solely responsible for any inaccurate or incomplete shipping information. All items purchased from this Website are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier. In the event your order is lost during shipping, we will assist you in pursuing a claim with the shipper, but will not be liable for any orders which are lost during shipping or misdelivered.
Product Concepts/Unsolicited Submissions
Prolume does not accept unsolicited ideas, concepts, proposals or other submissions with respect to its existing or any new products.   By submitting any ideas, concepts, proposals or other submissions with respect to Prolume’s existing products or any new product, even if done in response to a request for feedback on a product from users, you automatically grant (or warrant that the owner of such rights has expressly granted) to Prolume a perpetual, royalty-free, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, and distribute your submission or incorporate your submission into any form, medium, or technology (now known or hereafter developed or devised) throughout the universe. In addition, you warrant that all so-called “moral rights” and other rights recognized throughout the world (including without limitation, the European Economic Community) in your submission have been waived and that Prolume has the unrestricted right to modify, edit, alter and change your submission without your or any other person’s consent.  There is no contract, implied or otherwise, that Prolume will compensate you for the use of your submission and, pursuant to the foregoing, Prolume will not compensate you for any such use.
Ownership of Intellectual Property/Restrictions on Use
All software, designs, text, images, photographs, illustrations, audio clips, video clips, artwork, graphic material, data and other copyrightable elements, and the selection and arrangements thereof, and all trademarks, service marks, trade dress and trade names which are part of or displayed through this Website (the “Materials”) are the property of Prolume and are protected, without limitation, pursuant to U.S. and foreign copyright and trademark laws.
You should assume that everything you see or read on this Website, receive through related services, or download from our servers, is protected by copyright unless otherwise stated and may only be used according to these Terms of Use. Prolume does not warrant or represent that your use of materials displayed on this Website will not infringe rights of third parties whom are not owned or affiliated with Prolume. Images are either Prolume’s property or used by Prolume with another party’s permission. The use of these images by you, or anyone else authorized by you, is prohibited unless specifically permitted by these Terms of Use. Any unauthorized use of such images may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, as well as other communications regulations and statutes.
Prolume, NanoLight, NanoFuel, NanoTools and other names used on this Website are the registered and unregistered trademarks of Prolume.  The trademarks (including the foregoing trademarks), logos, and service marks (collectively the “Trademarks”) displayed on this Website are registered and unregistered trademarks of Prolume or of third parties who have authorized Prolume to use the Trademarks. Your misuse of the Trademarks displayed on this Website, or any other content on this Website, except as provided herein, is strictly prohibited. Nothing contained on this Website should be construed as granting any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on this Website without the written permission of Prolume or such third party that may own the Trademark.
These Terms of Use grant to you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to access and use this Website and the Materials for your personal, non-commercial use. Except as expressly provided herein, you agree that no portion of this Website will be accessed, used, reproduced, duplicated, copied, or otherwise exploited by you for any other purpose; that you have obtained no other rights, titles or interests of any kind in or to this Website or the Materials; and that nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring any other right, title or interest.  As between you and Prolume, all rights in the Materials and the Website are reserved to Prolume.
The following applies to all portions of the Website which are downloaded by you:  Prolume hereby grants you a personal, non-exclusive, non-assignable, revocable, non-transferable license to use and display, for noncommercial and personal use only, one copy of appropriately limited portions of the Materials and/or software that are downloadable from this Website, including, without limitation, any files, codes, audio, or images incorporated in or generated by or in conjunction with the Website and/or Prolume, provided that “Copyright Prolume, LTD. All Rights Reserved. Used With Permission.” accompanies all copyrightable Materials and other notices are properly maintained. Modification of Materials or use of Materials for any other purpose is a violation of Prolume’s copyright and other proprietary rights. For purposes of these Terms of Use, use of any Materials in any unauthorized manner (including, without limitation, on web pages or sites that contain paid or free advertisements, third-party endorsements of any kind or nature (including without limitation, endorsements of a religious, political, or social orientation nature), or promotions; or sell or offer products, games, or services; or any other content which Prolume in its sole and absolute discretion deems inappropriate) is strictly prohibited. You agree not to reproduce, modify, create derivative works from, display, perform, publish, distribute, disseminate, broadcast, sell, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, or circulate any Materials to any third party (including, without limitation, display and distribute the Materials via a third party website) without Prolume’s express prior written consent. Unauthorized or prohibited exploitation of Materials may subject you to civil liability and criminal prosecution under applicable federal and state laws.
Disclaimers/Limitation of Liability
THIS WEBSITE AND ALL MATERIALS CONTAINED ON IT ARE DISTRIBUTED AND TRANSMITTED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, PROLUME DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. PROLUME DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE SITE OR MATERIALS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. PROLUME DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN IT WITH REGARD TO THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, AND VALIDITY OF ANY MATERIAL RESTS WITH YOU.  YOU, NOT PROLUME, ASSUME THE COMPLETE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR, OR CORRECTION.
APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MODIFY AND/OR DISCONTINUE THIS WEBSITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
TO THE EXTENT THAT YOU COMMUNICATE WITH PROLUME’S CUSTOMER SERVICE DEPARTMENT OR A PROLUME REPRESENTATIVE THROUGH ANY SOURCE, THE STATEMENTS, PROMISES OR ACTIONS TAKEN BY SUCH SOURCES SHALL NOT LIMIT OR OTHERWISE MODIFY THE TERMS OF THIS DISCLAIMER AND/OR THIS USER AGREEMENT AND THIS DISCLAIMER AND THESE TERMS OF USE SHALL APPLY TO ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED TO YOU THROUGH SUCH SOURCES.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, PROLUME, ITS AFFILIATES, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, LICENSORS, REPRESENTATIVES, AND THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS TO THIS WEBSITE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, COMPENSATORY, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR SIMILAR DAMAGES, THAT MAY RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE MATERIALS CONTAINED ON THIS WEBSITE, WHETHER THE MATERIAL IS PROVIDED OR OTHERWISE SUPPLIED BY PROLUME, YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY AND REGARDLESS OF WHETHER PROLUME IS AWARE OF OR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, YOU WAIVE CALIFORNIA CIVIL CODE SECTION 1542, WHICH SAYS: “A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST INHIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH, IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR.”
WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, IN NO EVENT SHALL PROLUME HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY CLAIMS, DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE) EXCEEDING THE AMOUNT PAID BY YOU, IF ANY, FOR ACCESSING THIS SITE.
Links/Linking
This Website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties, including buttons which allow you to like or dislike a particular product or feature. The linked sites are not under the control of Prolume, and Prolume is not responsible for the content available on any other websites linked to this Website. Such links do not imply Prolume’s endorsement of material on any other website and Prolume disclaims all liability with regard to your access to such linked websites. Prolume provides links to other websites as a convenience to users and access to any other websites linked to this Website is at your own risk and is subject to that website’s terms of use and privacy policy.
Emails
You agree that these Terms of Use, including but not limited to the Disclaimers and Limitations of Liability, apply to all emails and other electronic communications which you receive from Prolume as though such email or other electronic communication and all of its content were a page of this Website.
Security of Information
We have put physical, electronic and managerial procedures into place in order to help safeguard and prevent unauthorized access, use and/or disclosure of your personally identifiable information. Although we use reasonable efforts to safeguard the security of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made on or through the internet and personally identifiable information stored on our servers or the servers of third parties that we use are vulnerable to attack and cannot be guaranteed to be secure. In addition, submissions made via email are not protected by encryption and are vulnerable to interception during transmission. We disclaim responsibility for all negligent acts that may result in the unauthorized use and/or disclosure of your personal information.
Ads and Malware
We take great care and pride in creating this Website. We are always on the lookout for technical glitches that effect how the Website works. When we find them on our end, we will fix them. Unfortunately, your home computer may cause some glitches that effect how you see our Website and that is beyond our control. If you experience any unusual behavior, content or ads on the Website, it may be the result of Malware on your computer. Malware includes computer viruses, key loggers, malicious active content, rogue programs and dialers, among others. While we continuously work closely with our partners to ensure that everything on the Website is working properly, sometimes Malware programs on your personal computer may interfere with your experience on our Website and on other sites that you visit. Please note that we cannot be responsible for the effects of any third-party software including Malware on your computer system.
Denial of Access
Prolume, for any reason and at its sole discretion, may decide that any person shall be denied access to any part of the Website. The sending of an email notice by Prolume to any email address associated with the denial shall constitute complete and sufficient notice of the denial. By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you agree to cease and desist immediately from any attempt to access the Website upon issuance of a denial. If you do not cease and desist, you hereby consent to an injunction to be entered against you by a court of competent jurisdiction, as provided herein, permanently enjoining you from attempting to access the Website, without Prolume having to post any bond or surety therefor.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Prolume, its affiliates, and their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, representatives, and third party providers to the Website from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from any violation of these Terms of Use by you. Prolume reserves the right to assume, at its sole expense, the exclusive defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will fully cooperate with Prolume in asserting any available defenses.
Jurisdiction
The Terms of Use and all matters or issues collateral thereto will be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Arizona applicable to contracts executed and performed entirely therein (without regard to any principles of conflicts of laws). You hereby agree that any action at law or in equity arising out of or relating to these Terms of Use or the site shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in Phoenix, Arizona. Further, you hereby expressly consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, Prolume shall be entitled to seek in any court of appropriate jurisdiction equitable or injunctive relief to enforce these Terms of Use.
If you use this Website from other locations you are responsible for compliance with local laws and regulations. Prolume products are available in many parts of the world; however, this Website may describe products that are not available in your jurisdiction.
Modification of Terms
Prolume may at any time revise these Terms of Use by updating the same at this Website without prior notice. Your continued use of this Website after such changes are posted will constitute your acceptance of such changes.
General
This agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and Prolume with respect to this Website and related services and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous terms or conditions, oral or written, between user and Prolume. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. Any cause of action arising out of or related to this Website or its service must commence within one (1) year after the cause of action arose; otherwise, such cause of action is permanently barred.
